A Guide to the Papers of James Taylor Ellyson, 1865, 1896-1910
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
City of Petersburg (1909 May 8)
Commercial Organizations (from Southern Commercial Congress)
(1909 Dec 20)
Conway, J.H. (1909 Sept 11)
Copeland, W.S. (1909 Sept 22)
Cridler and Kohlsaat (1907 Mar 6)
Cuchins, Sol. (1905 Mar 17)
Cumming, H.J. (1909 Aug 3)
C.W. Antrim & Sons (1899 Dec 6)
Dabney, W.T. (1908 Dec 31; 1909 Jan 4, Jan 7, Jan 16)
Daniel, John W. (1908 Jan 6, Jan 25)
Davis, Charles Hall (1909 Dec 24)
DeVault, M.T. (1909 Nov 24)
DeVault, M.T. (1909 Jan 2, Jan 7, Jan 12; 1910 Oct 1, n.d.)
Downing, T.J. (1909 Dec 24)
Editors of the South (from Southern Commercial Congress)
(1909 Dec 20)
Ellett, Miss Sarah (1909 Nov 17)
Ellyson, G.D. (1909 Dec 28)
Ellyson, Onan (1909 Nov 30)
Feild, Thomas L. (1909 Aug 4, Aug 30, Nov 30)
Finch, Allen W. (1909 Dec 30)
Gilliam, Robert (1909 Dec 27)
Goad, E.V. (1909 Aug 31)
Goolrick, John T. (1909 Sept 13)
Green, Raleigh T. (1909 Dec 27; 1910 Jan 10)
Hamilton, R.P. (1908 Dec 4; 1909 Dec 24)
Harlow, M.B. (1909 Apr 22)
Hash, W.A. (1909 Sept 11)
Hayes, J.A. (1909 Oct 13)
Heath, Miss Nannie Randolph (1909 Sept 21)
Henderson, J.T. (1909 Aug 24)
Hiden, and Rixey Messrs. (1909 Sept 11)
Hinds & Noble, Publishers, New York (1909 Sept 27)
Howard, R.J. (1909 Jan 27)
Hyatt, Hallett (1907 Mar 18; 1909 Mar 13)
Jacobs, B.A. (1909 Sept 27)
James, B.O. (1909 Nov 2)
James, R.A. (1909 Dec 27)
Jones, C.E. (1909 Sept 11)
Jones, Joseph J. (1909 Apr 13)
Kenon, Thomas S. (1909 Aug 9)
Knickerbocker Trust Company (1909 Nov 27)
Kohlsaat and Cridler (1907 Mar 9)
Krause, Mrs. William (1908 Oct 27)
Lamb, John (1909 Nov 30)
Lloyd, James W. (1909 Jun 12)
Madison, E.C. (1900 May 9)
Martin, Alvah H. (1909 Jan 28)
Marye, Morton (1909 Sept 17)
Matthews, M.B. (1909 Dec 31)
McHugh, Charle A. (1909 Dec 31)
McKean, W.S. (1909 Sept 17)
Meredith, Wyndham R. (1909 Nov 23)
Minor, Mrs. Kate P. (1909 Jan 20)
Moon, J.W. (1905 Jun 24)
Moore, Edgar B. (1909 Apr 27, May 14)
Murrell, George E. (1905 Jun 24)
Neblett, J.T. (1909 Jan 5)
Nicholson, D.A. (1905 Jun 24)
Parker, John M. (1909 Dec 22)
Philips, Mrs. H.C. (1909 Dec 28)
Post Dispatch, St. Louis, Missouri (1907 Nov 4)
Potts, H. (1907 Apr 1)
Reed, Stuart F. (1909 Aug 9)
Richmond City Council (1903 Jun 2)
Richmond Street Sprinkling Company (1907 Apr 6)
Rixey and Hiden, Messrs. (1909 Sept 11)
Robinson, Bird M. (1909 Mar 16, Mar 22, Apr 8, Apr 12, May 28, Jun 15, Jun 22, Sept 17, Sept 20, Oct 11, Dec 20, Dec 29)
R. Taylor & Company (1909 Nov 2)
Ryan, Thomas Fortune (1908 Dec 3)
Ryland, Charles H. (1909 Jan 5, Jan 7, Jan 18, Jan 30)
Simmerman, S.S. (1910 Aug 10)
Shackelford, George S. (1909 Nov 29)
Shepherd, C.N. (1909 Sept 10)
Smith, Thomas (1909 Oct 25)
Southern Railway Company (1909 Jan 15)
Stark, Thomas H. (1909 Sept 24)
Stillwell, J.F. (1909 Feb 2)
Strudwick, E. and 16 other men (1908 Nov 23)
Sumpter, E.E. (1909 Nov 29)
Sydnor, R.W. (1905 Jun 24)
Turner, Peyton E. (1910 Sept 19)
Tyler, Hoge J. (1909 Oct 25)
Umstadter Myers Company (1908 Jan 27)
Virginia Unionist (1909 Aug 9)
West, J.E. (1905 Apr 1; 1909 Dec 27, Dec 30)
Wev., Mrs. Nellie D. (1909 Dec 4)
White, Robert (1909 Sept 27, Nov 17, Nov 30)
Whitehead, I.P. (1909 Dec 4)
Williams, W.H. (1905 Mar 15)
Willcox, J.W. (1908 Dec 4; 1909 Mar 3)
Church Form Letters (1899 Nov 29; 1902 Aug 22)
Virginia State Democratic Committee Form Letters (1905 Apr 26; 1906 Oct 9; 1907 Mar 1;1909 Oct 18)
Joseph Bryan Memorial Association Form Letters (1908 Dec 29)
Invitations, Unidentified (1909, May 8)
Education Board of the Baptist General Association of Virginia Form Letter (1909 Sept 10)
Letter re First Company of Richmond Howitzers (1909 Sept 15)
Contents List
- Civil War Papers 1865 (Box 1)
  Includes last muster roll of Virginia Artillery, Richmond Howitzers, 2nd Company, at Appomattox, Va.
- Correspondence of J. Taylor Ellyson 1895-1900 Jun, 6 folders (Box 1)
- Correspondence of J. Taylor Ellyson 1900 Jul-1906 Feb, 7 folders (Box 2)
- Correspondence of J. Taylor Ellyson 1906 Mar-1908, 9 folders (Box 3)
- Correspondence of J. Taylor Ellyson 1909 Jan-Nov, 8 folders (Box 4)
- Correspondence of J. Taylor Ellyson 1909 Dec-1910, n.d., 7 folders (Box 5)
- Invitations to J. Taylor Ellyson ca. 1902-1907 (Box 6)
- Jamestown Exposition 1907 (Box 6)
- Legal & Financial Papers 1899-1909 (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous 1898-1910 (Box 6)
- News clippings re Ellyson's Canvass for Lt. Governor 1900-1906 (Box 6)
- Political Papers 1897-1908 (Box 6)